<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Coroutines Android</string>
    <string name="testingText">
        Hi,

I can help you develop the COVID-19 fighting App in Flutter and using Firebase Realtime Database. I can also convert the Figma Designs into Flutter Responsive Screens. I fully understand the Material Design Guidelines.

I have already developed and published a few apps in Flutter using Firebase Realtime Database. You can check it here: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.muhsanapps.notes

NOTE: I have more projects that are done in Flutter but I am sending you only the most relevant project.

As a Google Certified Developer, I can help you complete this project with the highest quality and within the timeline. Iam also excellent with Version Controlling and Project Management.

I can also provide you money-back guarantee and support after completing the project. I can also answer your messages within 10-20 minutes.

Do you have any designs ready for the project? Can  I see them? Also, can you share the technical requirements document with me?

Looking forward to hearing from you.

Regards
Muhsan Javed
Intermediate Android Developer

QA

How much  are you familiar with Flutter?
I have One-plus years of experience developing Flutter Applications. I have used complete Firebase Tools in Flutter. Please read my cover letter to know more.



What was the most recent project that you used Firebase Database (or Firestore) and what did you use it for?
I have already developed and published a few apps in Flutter using Firebase Realtime Database. You can check it here: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.muhsanapps.notes

I have used the Firebase Realtime Database and Firestore in different projects of Flutter.

Mainly for as a complete backend of the app, for chatting purpose and complete CRM. ..



Please tell us about the most interesting Flutter Project that you worked on and why it is. Please share a link to the app if available.?
1- Taking Notes App
      https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.muhsanapps.notes



Do you have any questions about us and /or about the project?
Do you have any designs ready for the project? Can  I see them? Also, can you share the technical requirements document with me?


When can you start working?
I am available to start immediately. Thank you for reading my proposal.

Looking forward to hearing from you.




    </string>
</resources>